Guide to the University Photography records, [ca.1989-2001]
University Photography records,
- Faculty and staff
  - C-D
    - Day, Christine, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Dealy, Katie, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Dean, Christiana, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Dean, Gwendolyn, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Dean, John, 1990-1996 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Dean, Sheila, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - DeBary, Brett, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - DeCicca, Phillip, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Decker, Dan, 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 90)
      One photograph undated. Negatives included
    - Degaetano, Arthur, 1998-2001 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Degloria, Steve, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Degraba, Sue, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Deinert, Herbert, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Dejong, Walter, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Demas, Antonia, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Dentes, John, 1994-2001 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Depoe, Richard, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Derry, Louis, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - DeStefano, Joanne, 1993-2002 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Detzer, Sharon, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Dev, Chekitan, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Devault, Eileen, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Devlin, Tom, 1992-1995 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Devgood, Tim, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 105)
      Negatives only. Article included
    - DeVries, Henry, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Dewinter, Urban, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Diaz, Jurabe, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Diciccio, Tom, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Dick, Richard, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Dieckmann, Rudiger, 1991-2003 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Dietert, Rodney, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Dietrich, Penny, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Dimunation, Mark, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - DiSalvo, Frank, 1999-2002 (Box 3, Folder 115)
      One set of photos undated. Negatives included
    - DiTommaso, Tony, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Dittman, David, 1992-1998 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Dobson, Alan, 1984-1995 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Donovan, Brian, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Dorcey, Tim, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Dorosh, Paul, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Dotson, Arch, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Douglas, Carlisle, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Doyle, Jeff, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Dozier, Eleanor, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Draper, E. Linn, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Dreher, Amy, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Drell, Persis, 1998-2002 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Drietzer, Richard, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Drinkwater, Laurie, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Drogo, Barb, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - D'Souza, Julia, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Dubori, Ed, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Duesino, Mike, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Dunifon, Rachel, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Dunlop, David, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Dunning, David, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Durkin, Nikki, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Durrett, Rick, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Duttweiler, Michael, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Dyckman, Thomas, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Dyer, Lee, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Ealick, Steve, 1992-2001 (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - E-F
    - Earl, Brian, 1989-1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - East, Elizabeth, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Eastman, Judith, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Eastman, Laurie, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Eastman, Lester, 1986-2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Eaton, Bill, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Eberhardt, Marian, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Eberts, Paul, 1990-1998 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Eckenrode, John, 1993-2002 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Edgar, Jamie, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Edmundson, Locksley, 1995-2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Edwards, Lawrence, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Ehrenberg, Ron, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Eisner, Mark, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Eisner, Thomas, 1969-2001 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      Two undated photographs, negatives included
    - Elber, Ron, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Elder, Glen, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Eldred, Terry, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Ellerbrock, Roy, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Elliot, Jack, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Elliot, John, 1993-2002 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Ellis, Yvonne, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Ellner, Stephen, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Elrod, Charles, 1992-1995 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Elser, Veit, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Emlen, Stephen, 1970-1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Enck, Jody, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Engst, Elaine, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Engstrom, James, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Entremont, Bob D., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Enz, Cathy, 1992-2001 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Ernenwein, Susan, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Escobar, Jose, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Escobedo, Fernando, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Esman, Milton, 1980-2003 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Esquivel, Kety, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      Photos of two different people, a man and a woman
    - Evans, Gary, 1995-2003 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Everett, Bob, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      Undated photograph and negative
    - Evett, Ken, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Ewert, Merrill, 1993-1998 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Ewert, Priscilla, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Eyck, Peter, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Eydt, Fred, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Eyster, James, 1991-1997 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Faber, Mary, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Fadden, JJ, 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Fadden, Mary, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Falvey, Mary, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Fan, Daisy, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Fara, Michael, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Farber, Hank, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Farina, Cynthia, 1987-2000 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Farley, Donald, 1998-2002 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Faulkner, Rick, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Fawcett, Nathan, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Fay, Charles, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Fay, Robert, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Feldshun, David, 1984-1992 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Fernandes, Erick, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Fernandez, Carlos, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Ferreira, Joan, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Fey, Nancy, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Fick, Gary, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Fields, Gary, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Figueroa, Enrique, 1992-1994 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Finch, Leslie, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Fine, Terrence, 1999-2002 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Fineman, Martha, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Firebaugh, Francille, 1986-2002 (Box 4, Folder 69)
      Negatives and a CD included
    - Fisher, Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Fisher, Joan, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Flahive, Matthew, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Flanagan, Leo, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Flanders, James, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Flansburgh, Earl, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Flynn, Nancy, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Foote, Robert, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Ford, Hilary, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Ford, John, 1980-1997 (Box 4, Folder 79)
      One photograph and negative undated
    - Fornum, Cornelia, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Fortes, Mayor, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Foster, Kelly, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Foulkes, Tom, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Fox, Danny, Undated (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Fox, Raymond, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Fox, Tom, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Fraboni, Tony, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Frank, Robert, 1985-2002 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Frechet, Jean, 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Freed, Jack, 1992-2001 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - French, Lori, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Frey, Margaret, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Fried, Al, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Friedan, Betty, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 94)
      Negatives and memorandum included
    - Friedman, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 95)
      Last name only
    - Friedman, Barbara, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 96)
    - Fuchs, Kent, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 97)
    - Fukuyama-Messenger, Francis, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 98)
    - Fulton, Alice, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 99)
    - Fussman, George, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - G-H
    - Gadoury, David, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 101)
    - Gaeta, Alexander, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 102)
    - Gaffney, Mike, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 103)
    - Gainor, Ellen, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 104)
    - Galindo, Dan, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 105)
    - Galton, David, 1976-1999 (Box 4, Folder 106)
    - Ganem, Claude, Undated (Box 4, Folder 107)
    - Garbarino, James, 1994-2000 (Box 4, Folder 108)
      Negatives and notes on a video conference included
    - Garcia, Ephrahim, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 109)
    - Garcia, Maria, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 110)
    - Garci̒a-Rivera, Andres, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 111)
    - Garrett, Charlene, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 112)
    - Garrison, Terry, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 113)
    - Garrow, Scott, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 114)
    - Garvey, Steven, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 115)
    - Garza, Cutberto, 1992-1998 (Box 4, Folder 116)
      Email and negatives included
    - Gassar, Linda, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 117)
    - Gates, Jeff, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 118)
    - Gates, Paul, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 119)
    - Gay, Geri, 1986-2003 (Box 4, Folder 120)
    - Geddes, Daryl, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 121)
    - Gehrke, Johannes, 1999-2003 (Box 4, Folder 122)
    - Gellar, Neal, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 123)
    - Gellert, George, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 124)
    - Gellert, Paul, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 125)
    - Genova, Paul, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 126)
    - George, Al, 1998-2000 (Box 4, Folder 127)
    - Georgi, Jay, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 128)
    - Gephel, Tenzin, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 129)
      Negatives and postcard only
    - Gerish, Peter, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Germain, Claire, 1996-2003 (Box 4, Folder 131)
    - German, Gene, 1990-2000 (Box 4, Folder 132)
    - Gerner, Jennifer, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 133)
    - Gerstein, Lynn, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Geske, Anna, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Giannelis, Emmanuel, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Gibbs, James, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Gibson, Kathleen, 2000-2003 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Gibson, Scott, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Gierasch, Peter, 1979-2001 (Box 4, Folder 140)
      Negatives and a photocopy included
    - Gilbert, Laurene, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Gillespie, Ardyth, 1980-1995 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Gillman, Richard, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Gilman, Sander, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Gilovich, Tom, 1993-1999 (Box 4, Folder 145)
      One photo undated
    - Ginnegar, Peter, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 146)
    - Ginsparg, Paul, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 147)
    - Giovanelli, Riccardo, 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 148)
    - Giovannoni, James, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 149)
    - Glasgow, Nina, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 150)
    - Glazer, Benjamin, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 151)
    - Gleason, Thomas, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Glynn, Carol, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Gold, Thomas, 1966-1997 (Box 4, Folder 154)
      One photograph undated, article included
    - Goldman, Emily, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Goldsby, Jackie, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Goldsmith, Paul, 1992-1999 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Photocopies included
    - Goldsmith, William, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Goldstein, Carolyn, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Gomes, Carla, 1999-2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Good, George, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Good, Henry, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Goodall, Jane, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Goodwin, Steve, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Gore, Albert, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Two headshots
    - Gorewit, Ron, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Gortzig, Carl, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Gossett, James, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Gottfried, Kurt, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Gotto, Antonio M., Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Gottschalk, Katherine, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Gouldin, Fred, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Gracen, Vernon, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Graff, Delia, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Granados, Robert, 1992-2001 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Grant, Mary Beth, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Green, Jennifer, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Green, Randy, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Greenberg, Don, 1976-1988 (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Two photos undated
    - Greene, Jennifer, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Greene, K., 1999 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Greenstein, Doreen, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Greenwood, Davydd, 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Gries, David, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Grinstein, Yaniv, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Grogan, Soneeta, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Grohn, Yrjo, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Grossvogel, David I., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Grossvogel, Jill, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Gruner, Sol, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Guckenheims, John, 1996-2003 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Gunkel, Wesley, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Gupta, Puja, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Gupta, Sachin, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Gurak, Douglas, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Gurazier, Kyle, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Gutman, Rebecca, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Haas, Jere, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Haas, Martine, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Habicht, Jean-Pierre, 1996-2003 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      One undated photograph and photocopy. Negatives included
    - Hadrovic, Peter, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Hahn, Alan, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Hahn, Dan Maloney, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Haine, Peggy, 1986-1995 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      One photograph undated. CD included
    - Hairston, Nelson George, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Haith, Douglas, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Haldemon, Jim, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Hall, Bill, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Hall, Tanni, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Halloron, Brian, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Halpern, Bruce, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Halpern, Joe, 2001-2003 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Halseth, Don, 1991-1998 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Hamilton, Scott, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Hamilton, Stephen, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Hamilton, Steve and Maryagnus, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Hamlin, Sue, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Hammer, David, 1986-2003 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Hammer, Tove, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Hammond, Jane, Undated (Box 5, Folder 65)
      Undated negatives
    - Hang, Y.D., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Hansel, William, Undated (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Hanson, Maureen, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Harch, Ann, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Hardesty, Jim, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Harding, Martha, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Hardwood, Ed, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Hardy, Ralph, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Harkness, Ellen, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Harrington, Laura, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Harris, Leonard, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Harris, Robert, 1979-2000 (Box 5, Folder 77)
      Negatives with Lee C. Lee from 1997 included
    - Harrison, Ellen, 1993-2002 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Harris-Warrick, Ron, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Harris-Warrick, Wendy, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Hart, Roger, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 81)
      Press release and description of photos included
    - Hartmanis, Junis, 1993-2003 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Hartnett, John, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Hass, Jerome, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Hassan, Salah, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 85)
      Negatives and an undated CD included
    - Hattery, Mike, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Hausner, Randy, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Hawks, Rod, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Hay, George, 1980-2000 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Hayes, Donald, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Hayes, Valerie, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Haynes, Martha, 1989-2001 (Box 5, Folder 92)
      Negatives and photocopies included
    - Hayward, Bud, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Hazan, Cindy, 1993-2000 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Healey, Timothy, 1988-2004 (Box 5, Folder 95)
      No photos attached to 2004 photo request
    - Hearst, Alice, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 96)
      Negatives only, Ted Lowi in pictures as well
    - Heck, Ramona, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Hedge, Alan, 1991-2004 (Box 5, Folder 98)
      No photos attached to 2004 photo request. Negatives and photocopies included
    - Hedlund, Dalva, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Heffron, Sandy, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Heinrich, Mark, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Heiser, John, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Hemani, Sheila, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Henderson, Chuck, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Henderson, David, 1986-1998 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Henderson, John, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Henderson, Pam, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Henderson, Shane, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Henion, Jack, 1992-1999 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Henkel, Jackie, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Henry, Franklin, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Henry, Susan, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Heppel, Leon, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Herrala, Alfred, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Herrin, Lamar, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Herter, Terry, 1994-1999 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Hickerson, Tom, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Hicks, Jim, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Hiebar, Neil, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Hiens, Mary, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Hilgartner, Stephen, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Hill, Collin, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Hill, Patti, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Hillman, Robert, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Hillman, Thomas, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Hinchey, Maurice, 1994-2000 (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Hine, Patricia, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Hines, Melissa, 1994-2001 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Hinkin, Timothy, 1992-1998 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Hinman, Don, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Hintz, Harold, 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 131)
      Two undated photographs
    - Hirschl, Thomas, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Hisle, James, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Hite, Molly, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Hittleman, Margo, 1993-1995 (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Hjortshoj, Keith, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 136)
      Descriptions of some photographs included, negatives included
    - Ho, Wilson, 1988-1999 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Hodge, Kathy, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Hodges, Marjorie, 1994-1999 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Hodnett, Ross, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Hoebeke, Richard, 1982-2001 (Box 5, Folder 141)
      Negatives and an article included
    - Hoffman, Linda, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Hoffman, Roald, 1978-1995 (Box 5, Folder 143)
      Undated photographs and negatives. Articles included
    - Hofher, Jim, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 144)
      One photograph undated, negatives included
    - Hogarth, Jeanne, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - Hohendahl, Peter, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - Holcomb, Don, 1971-1992 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Holden-Smith, Barbara, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Hollern, Susan, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Holmes, Catherine, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Hong, Youn-Ho, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Hopcroft, John, 1988-2003 (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Hopkins, Carl, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - Horst, Ken, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Hostetler, Michael, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Hotchkiss, Joseph, 1993-2002 (Box 5, Folder 156)
      Negatives with description included
    - Houck, James, 1972-1995 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - Houghton, George, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Houphton, James R., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Houpt, Katherine, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - House, Ron, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Houston, Paul, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Hover, Kenneth, 1986-1999 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Howard, Russ, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Howell, Russell, 1992-1997 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Howland, Howard, 1992-2003 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Howland-Bolton, Richard, 1990-1995 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Howley, Tom, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Hoy, Ron, 1984-2002 (Box 5, Folder 169)
      Negatives included. Item from 2002 is only a job order
    - Hribar, Paul, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 170)
      Negatives and photocopy only.
    - Hsu, John, 1988-2001 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      One photograph undated. Negatives, press release, and photocopies included
    - Hubbel, Kent, 1993-2001 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Hudler, George, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Hudson, Michael, 1990-1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Huettman, Elizabeth, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Huffaker, Timothy, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Huffington, Arianna, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Hughes, Eileen, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Hughes, Patrick, 1992-2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Hull, Isabel, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Huller, Ted, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Hulslander, Sara, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Hunt, Jane, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Hunt, Melissa Thomas, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Hunter, Jean, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Hurd, Richard, 1994-1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Husa, Karel, 1986-1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      Undated photographs and negatives included. Includes correspondence between Husa and CU photography as well
    - Husa, Karel, 1966-1990 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      Undated photographs, photocopies included
    - Husa, Karel, 1966-1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      Undated photograph, negatives included
    - Hussey, Jennifer, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Husted-Medvec, Victoria, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Huttenlocher, Daniel, 1993-2003 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Hyams, Paul, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Hysell, David, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - I-K
    - Idris, Havva, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Ingraffea, Anthony, 1985-1995 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Ink, Elaine, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Irish, Bill, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Irwin, Lynne, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Isaacson, Michael, 1982-1998 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Undated negatives included. Press release included
    - Isabel, Billy Jean, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Isacks, Brian, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Jacobs, Nancy, Undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Jacobson, Jay, 1980-1989 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - James, Erin, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Janis, Ralph, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Janowitz, Phyllis, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Jasanoff, Sheila, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Jasper, Paul, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Jelinsky, Lynn, 1991-1998 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Jemison, Mae, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Jenkins, Bill, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Jenkins, James, 1990-1994 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Jennings, Jan, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Jensen, Barbara, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Jensen, Neal, Undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Jessler, Allan R., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Jirousek, Charlotte, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Joachims, Thorsten, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Johansson, Steve, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Johnson, Helen, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Johnson, Justin, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Johnson, Keith, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Johnson, Richard, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Johnson, Robert, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Johnson, Scott, 1997-2002 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Johnson, Sheri, 1989-1994 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Johnson, Steve, 1991-2002 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      Undated CD
    - Johnston, Jim, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Johnstone, Bruce, Undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Jones, Lawerence, Undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Jones, Scott, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Jones, Tom, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Joo, Yong, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Jordan, Kim, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Jordan, Terry, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Jordan-Mount, Valerie, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Jorling, Thomas, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 68)